Brother San,
الأخ سان ،
your brother has been gone for seven years,
ذهب أخوك منذ سبع سنوات ،
Why do you use ventriloquism to learn how to speak from him?
لماذا تستخدم التكلم من بطنه لتتعلم كيف تتحدث منه؟
What ventriloquism?
ما الكلام من بطنه؟
He's not dead.
لم يمت.
Every day, he taught me how to manage the villa,
علمني كل يوم كيفية إدارة الفيلا ،
how to hold a Sword Worship Conference?
كيف تعقد مؤتمر عبادة السيف؟
He returned,
هو عاد،
Take a look.
إلق نظرة.
Tang Mu Feng,
تانغ مو فنغ ،
this is your brother's tablet,
هذا هو لوح أخيك ،
It's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Brother still talks to me every day,
لا يزال الأخ يتحدث معي كل يوم ،
he can't be
لا يمكنه أن يكون
one of them.
واحد منهم.
They're the ones who killed him.
إنهم من قتلوه.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
They must have killed him.
يجب أن يكونوا قد قتلوه.
I'm going to kill them!
سأقتلهم!
Kill them!
اقتلهم!
Mu Feng, do you really plan
مو فنغ ، هل تخطط حقًا
to live in the shadows for the rest of your life?
لتعيش في الظل لبقية حياتك؟
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
So that you can wake me up.
حتى تتمكن من إيقاظي.
Ladies and gentlemen,
سيداتي وسادتي،
fellow countrymen and folks,
رفقاء الوطن والناس ،
Welcome to the quadrennial Imperial Sword Villa.
مرحبًا بكم في فيلا Imperial Sword التي تُقام كل أربع سنوات.
The competition scene of Sword Worship Conference,
ساحة مسابقة مؤتمر عبادة السيف ،
this is the live broadcast of the competition
هذا هو البث المباشر للمسابقة
brought by Fankugua Newspaper.
جلبتها جريدة فانكوجوا.
In this competition,
في هذه المسابقة ،
the leading brand of Pepper,
العلامة التجارية الرائدة لشركة Pepper ،
Ouch Hello Chili Sauce Exclusive title
Ouch Hello Chili Sauce عنوان حصري
Chilli Sauce Only choose Ouch Hello.
صلصة الفلفل الحار فقط اختر Ouch Hello.
At the same time,
في نفس الوقت،
we would also like to thank the champion's preferred brand,
نود أيضًا أن نشكر العلامة التجارية المفضلة للبطل ،
Yuge's Four Treasures of the Study, and Shengji Money Store,
كنوز يوج الأربعة للدراسة ، ومتجر Shengji Money Store ،
which borrows money without asking relatives and friends,
التي تقترض المال دون أن تطلب من الأقارب والأصدقاء ،
for their generous sponsorship of this Sword Worship Conference.
لرعايتهم الكريمة لمؤتمر عبادة السيف هذا.
Now, let's follow the camera in front of us,
الآن ، دعنا نتبع الكاميرا التي أمامنا ،
and focus on the scene of the game.
والتركيز على مشهد اللعبة.
First of all,
أولا قبل كل شيء،
you'll see
سوف ترى
our ready-to-go competitors.
منافسينا الجاهزين للانطلاق.
According to the reporter's report,
وبحسب تقرير المراسل ،
all the competitors have taken antidiarrheal drugs.
تناول جميع المنافسين الأدوية المضادة للإسهال.
And I bought insurance.
واشتريت التأمين.
Some players
بعض اللاعبين
have even booked beds in the pharmacy in advance.
لقد حجزت أسرّة في الصيدلية مسبقًا.
To deal with the hot and painful baptism of this session.
للتعامل مع المعمودية الساخنة والمؤلمة لهذه الدورة.
Okay,
تمام،
now the judges at the scene,
الآن القضاة في مكان الحادث ،
Finally, to confirm the contestants of this session,
أخيرًا ، لتأكيد المتسابقين في هذه الدورة ،
all of you solemnly raise your hands,
ارفعوا أيديكم رسمياً ،
It means to participate in the competition,
تعني المشاركة في المسابقة ،
hey wait,
مهلا انتظر،
The Saint Girl of the Zoroastrianism doesn't seem to have
لا يبدو أن الفتاة القديسة الزرادشتية لديها
Ko Xiang Nai at her fingertips,
كو شيانغ ناي وأطراف أصابعها ،
Yes,
نعم،
we
نحن
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Although Song Ningyan retired,
على الرغم من تقاعد سونغ نينغيان ،
the Zoroastrianism still got the highest score in this round.
لا تزال الزرادشتية تحصل على أعلى الدرجات في هذه الجولة.
10 points,
10 نقاط ،
although we saw the players on the field
على الرغم من أننا رأينا اللاعبين في الملعب
complaining about the scoring rules,
يشكو من قواعد التسجيل ،
But it doesn't seem to affect
لكن لا يبدو أنه يؤثر
the normal progress of the game at all.
التقدم الطبيعي للعبة على الإطلاق.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
What's so great about being rich?
ما هو الشيء الرائع في كونك ثريًا؟
The first round
الجولة الأولى
begins.
يبدأ.
Okay,
تمام،
now the first round begins.
الآن تبدأ الجولة الأولى.
Zhou Luochen, a member of the blade master couple,
Zhou Luochen ، عضو في الزوجين الرئيسيين للشفرة ،
sniffed the fat pepper in his hand,
شم الفلفل السمين في يده ،
He bit it down without hesitation.
قام بقضمها دون تردد.
As if to say,
وكأنه يقول،
it's too simple.
انها بسيطة جدا.
The camera is given to Leng Wuyou.
تم منح الكاميرا إلى Leng Wuyou.
Judging from his micro-expression,
انطلاقا من تعبيره الدقيق ،
it's just a piece of cake.
انها مجرد قطعة من الكعكة.
Let's take a look at Su Qi's side.
دعنا نلقي نظرة على جانب Su Qi.
It seems that the clouds are pale and the wind is light,
يبدو أن الغيوم شاحبة والرياح خفيفة ،
but we can see from his pompous expression,
لكن يمكننا أن نرى من تعبيره الغريب ،
The tip of his tongue is burning.
طرف لسانه يحترق.
Hey, wait,
مهلا انتظر،
Li Xia,
لي شيا ،
Let's turn the camera to the other two contestants.
دعنا نحول الكاميرا إلى المتسابقين الآخرين.
I remember,
أتذكر،
you can't eat spicy food, right?
لا يمكنك تناول الطعام الحار ، أليس كذلك؟
Let's give in this time.
دعونا نستسلم في هذا الوقت.
Who are you? Do I know you?
من أنت؟  هل انا اعرفك؟
Li Xia,
لي شيا ،
stop being angry.
توقف عن الغضب.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
Li Xia. I'll eat it for you.
لي شيا.  سآكله من أجلك.
Why don't you give it to me?
لماذا لا تعطيه لي؟
I'll eat it for you.
سآكله من أجلك.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
I'll take care of you.
ساعتني بك.
I'll eat it for you.
سآكله من أجلك.
It's useless.
انها غير مجدية.
The elimination came quite suddenly.
جاء الإقصاء فجأة.
I didn't expect two players
لم أكن أتوقع لاعبين
to stop at the first round one after another,
للتوقف عند الجولة الأولى واحدًا تلو الآخر ،
We would also like to remind
نود أيضا أن نذكر
the audience who are watching the game,
الجمهور الذي يشاهد المباراة ،
Whether it's spicy or not varies from person to person.
سواء كان حارًا أم لا يختلف من شخص لآخر.
You like spicy food but you have to do what you can.
تحب الطعام الحار ولكن عليك أن تفعل ما تستطيع.
Okay Ladies and gentlemen,
حسناً سيداتي وسادتي ،
let's move on to the second round of the competition,
دعنا ننتقل إلى الجولة الثانية من المسابقة ،
Devil Green Pepper,
الفلفل الأخضر الشيطاني
We see that there are still three players on the field,
نرى أنه لا يزال هناك ثلاثة لاعبين في الملعب ،
some of whom take their time,
البعض منهم يأخذ وقته ،
Some players'expressions are distorted, some
بعض تعبيرات اللاعبين مشوهة والبعض الآخر
players still have the same style,
لا يزال لدى اللاعبين نفس الأسلوب ،
All right,
حسنا،
now let's take a look at the supporting letters from the contestants,
الآن دعونا نلقي نظرة على الرسائل الداعمة من المتسابقين ،
First,
أولاً،
No worries.
لا تقلق.
Embrace each other with true feelings.
احتضن بعضكما البعض بمشاعر حقيقية.
This can be seen as the support of General Shence,
يمكن اعتبار هذا على أنه دعم الجنرال شنس ،
Leng Wuyou,
لينغ ويو ،
Let's take a look at the next letter.
دعنا نلقي نظرة على الحرف التالي.
Sword Saint, Sword Saint,
قديس السيف ، قديس السيف ،
victory is on the flag,
النصر على العلم
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
They must be fans of Mr. and Mrs. Sword Saint.
يجب أن يكونوا من محبي السيد والسيدة Sword Saint.
Okay,
تمام،
Let's read the last letter,
دعنا نقرأ الحرف الأخير ،
Su Qi is not spicy enough
Su Qi ليس حارًا بدرجة كافية
to pay back the money.
لتسديد المال.
It's really a sudden peal of thunder.
إنها حقًا درع رعد مفاجئ.
While we were reading the letters from the fans,
بينما كنا نقرأ رسائل المعجبين ،
the winner of the second round had already been decided.
تم بالفعل تحديد الفائز في الجولة الثانية.
The eliminated contestants are representatives of the Beggars'Gang.
المتسابقون الذين تم استبعادهم هم ممثلو عصابة المتسولين.
Su Qi
سو تشي
Now let's put in a searching for you.
الآن دعنا نبدأ البحث عنك.
Okay,
تمام،
Thank you for your patience.
شكرا لك على صبرك.
Welcome back to the competition.
مرحبًا بك مرة أخرى في المنافسة.
From sunrise to sunset,
من شروق الشمس الى غروبها،
from cockcrow to barking,
من الديك إلى النباح ،
this part of the competition has finally come to the final round.
وصل هذا الجزء من المسابقة أخيرًا إلى الجولة النهائية.
Ouch! Desperate Soul-taking Pot is better than the live-eating scene.
أوتش!  وعاء أخذ الروح اليائسة أفضل من مشهد الأكل الحي.
I'm sure you've already noticed
أنا متأكد من أنك لاحظت بالفعل
the murderous copper pot on the table,
وعاء النحاس القاتل على الطاولة ،
Let me give you a brief introduction,
اسمحوا لي أن أقدم لكم مقدمة موجزة ،
this time's Death-take-away Pot,
وعاء اقتلاع الموت هذا الوقت ،
Use Ouch to feed chili sauce and all chilies above five-star spicy degree
استخدم Ouch لتغذية صلصة الفلفل الحار وجميع الفلفل الحار فوق درجة حارة من فئة الخمس نجوم
as raw materials and boil them for 991 days.
كمادة خام وتغلي لمدة 991 يومًا.
Smell it and you'll lose your sense of taste.
شمها وستفقد حاسة التذوق لديك.
If you lick it, you'll lose consciousness.
إذا لعقتها ، ستفقد وعيك.
If you take a sip,
إذا أخذت رشفة ،
oh my god.
يا إلهي.
I can't even think about it.
لا أستطيع حتى التفكير في الأمر.
I don't need it.
لا أحتاجه.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
I have a title,
لدي عنوان ،
His name is Little Prince of Sichuan.
اسمه الأمير الصغير لسيشوان.
Young Hero Leng,
يونغ هيرو لينغ ،
Please.
لو سمحت.
Childe Zhou.
تشيلدي تشو.
In my opinion,
فى رايى،
you'd better give in.
من الأفضل أن تستسلم.
Let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
As you can see,
كما ترون،
Zhou Luochen preferred the soul-returning pickled pepper as an appetizer.
فضل Zhou Luochen الفلفل المخلل الذي يعيد الروح كمقبلات.
Delicious.
لذيذ.
It's amazing.
شيء مذهل.
Ladies and gentlemen,
سيداتي وسادتي،
contestant Leng has not only chosen the soul-returning pickled pepper,
المتسابق لينغ لم يختار فقط الفلفل المخلل الذي يعيد الروح ،
And with Demon King Chili Sauce without humanity,
ومع صلصة الفلفل الحار ملك الشيطان بدون إنسانية ،
this way of eating,
طريقة الأكل هذه ،
I really don't want to leave any chance for my opponent.
لا أريد حقًا ترك أي فرصة لخصمي.
Let's see
دعونا نرى
how Player Zhou will respond?
كيف سيستجيب اللاعب تشو؟
There are two brushes
هناك نوعان من الفرش
for such a provocation.
لمثل هذا الاستفزاز.
Go on.
تابع.
That's right,
هذا صحيح،
Player Zhou really looked at another hot sauce on the field,
نظر اللاعب Zhou حقًا إلى صلصة حارة أخرى في الملعب ،
which was the legendary
الذي كان الأسطوري
Ouch Feed Ten Stars Spicy Scarlet Chili Sauce.
أوتش علف بصلصة الفلفل الحار القرمزي الحارة عشر نجوم.
Everyone, you must not underestimate this scarlet chili sauce,
الجميع ، يجب ألا تقلل من شأن صلصة الفلفل الحار القرمزية ،
which is known as the nightmare of rice,
الذي يعرف بكابوس الأرز ،
The terminator of noodles,
فاصل المعكرونة
just a little bit.
قليلا فقط.
You can eat these three bowls of rice together.
يمكنك أن تأكل هذه الأطباق الثلاثة من الأرز معًا.
Two bowls of noodles,
وعاءان من المعكرونة ،
and the more I eat, the more I want to eat.
وكلما أكلت أكثر ، كلما أردت أن آكل أكثر.
Become a roadblock on your way to lose weight.
كن عقبة في طريقك لخسارة الوزن.
Epitaph on the road to fitness,
مرثية على طريق اللياقة ،
now,
حاليا،
We saw that the two players who ate scarlet chili sauce
رأينا أن اللاعبين الذين أكلوا صلصة الفلفل الحار القرمزية
have already reacted.
لقد ردت بالفعل.
But he refused to compromise.
لكنه رفض المساومة.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Are they going to start?
هل سيبدأون؟
Childe Leng,
تشايلد لينغ ،
looking at your face, you don't change your color and your heart doesn't beat,
بالنظر إلى وجهك ، لا تغير لونك ولا ينبض قلبك ،
You won.
لقد فزت.
To you for being a hero.
لك لكونك بطلا.
After you,
بعدك،
Childe Zhou.
تشيلدي تشو.
You can treat me first.
يمكنك معاملتي أولا.
That's all.
هذا كل شئ.